<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<langText>

	<metadata>
		<title>
			<index>Danny Chandler's Amazing Swiss Slimming Concept | MySwissDiet</index>
			<danny>Danny L. Chandler | MySwissDiet</danny>
			<slimming>Slimming concept | MySwissDiet</slimming>
			<partnership>Partnership | MySwissDiet</partnership>
			<contact>Contact us | MySwissDiet</contact>
			<error>Something went wrong | MySwissDiet</error>
		</title>
	</metadata>

	<alt>
		<header>
			<en>English</en>
			<fr>French</fr>
			<ru>Russian</ru>
		</header>
		<index>
			<drinks>Healthy drinks</drinks>
			<proteins>Proteins</proteins>
			<slim>Slim body</slim>
			<salad>Healthy salad</salad>
			<danny>Danny L. Chandler</danny>
			<hands>Hands shaking</hands>
		</index>
	</alt>

	<menu>
		<m1>HOME</m1>
		<m2>DANNY L. CHANDLER</m2>
		<m3>SLIMMING CONCEPT</m3>
		<m4>PARTNERSHIP</m4>
		<m5>CONTACT</m5>
	</menu>

	<index>
		<title>DANNY CHANDLER’S AMAZING SWISS SLIMMING CONCEPT</title>
		<t1>
			Welcome to the official page of the Swiss weight-loss concept called "&lt;strong&gt;DANNY CHANDLER’S AMAZING SWISS SLIMMING CONCEPT&lt;/strong&gt;". I’d like to present this efficient method of weight-loss that I created as well as explain how it works. Do not hesitate to contact me should you be someone who wants to lose weight in a healthy manner or someone wanting to promote this diet in your region or country.
			&lt;br &gt; &lt;br &gt;
			I wish you all the best in your weight-loss efforts,
		</t1>
		<t2>
			Learn more about this efficient, safe and quick weight-loss method.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;a href="/slimming-concept"&gt;>> More&lt;/a&gt;
		</t2>
		<t3>
			This section of the site is about Danny L. Chandler, the mind behind the concept.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;a href="/danny-chandler"&gt;>> About&lt;/a&gt;
		</t3>
		<t4>
			We are looking for potential business partners in developing the dieting concept in their country or area.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;a href="/partnership"&gt;>> More&lt;/a&gt;
		</t4>
		<signature-title>Concept creator</signature-title>
		<get-in-touch-title>GET IN TOUCH</get-in-touch-title>
		<get-in-touch-text>Email us at &lt;a href="mailto:info@myswissdiet.com"&gt;info@myswissdiet.com&lt;/a&gt; or</get-in-touch-text>
		<get-in-touch-button>CONTACT US</get-in-touch-button>
	</index>

	<danny>
		<name>DANNY L. CHANDLER</name>
		<t1>
			&lt;li&gt;Studied 9 years in Zürich, Switzerland&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;4 years of formation as a druggist&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;3 years of formation in Sales and Marketing&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;A 25 year long career at Similasan SA, Switzerland (n.1 Homeopathy company in Switzerland and Austria)&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;ul&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Medical representative&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Director of Marketing and Sales&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;General director&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;/ul&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Native language: German &lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Other languages: English, French&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Started developing various health related concepts based on natural products and treatment of obesity 15 years ago &lt;/li&gt;
		</t1>
		<quote>
			During most of my professional life, I’ve tried to look for efficient alternatives which could act as substitutes to official medical procedures (while not acting against them!).
		</quote>
	</danny>

	<slimming>
		<h1>Slimming concept</h1>
		<t1>
			During most of my professional life, I’ve tried to look for efficient alternatives which could act as substitutes to official medical procedures (while not acting against them!) and measured them up to the following parameters:

			&lt;ul class="text-indentation no-list-style margin-top-20"&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="glyphicon glyphicon-ok-sign"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-18"&gt;Efficiency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="glyphicon glyphicon-ok-sign"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-18"&gt;Safety&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="glyphicon glyphicon-ok-sign"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-18"&gt;Practicality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="glyphicon glyphicon-ok-sign"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-18"&gt;Harmlessness for health &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</t1>
		<t2>
			One of the most important areas I have looked into were &lt;strong&gt;patients affected with obesity&lt;/strong&gt;. I was trying to find an easy, comprehensible and reliable method that would help patients lose weight once and for all. By &lt;strong&gt;easy to use&lt;/strong&gt;, I meant a program that is easy to abide by in daily life, so no counting calories or overly complicated to cook low-calorie meals. Something that anyone could follow. By &lt;strong&gt;reliability&lt;/strong&gt;, I meant a program that – if one abides by its rules – would bring results to practically any patient without exception. By &lt;strong&gt;comprehensible&lt;/strong&gt;, I meant a method that would introduce a system leading to success without fail. I wanted the method I pictured to be understood by anyone without needing medical education or having to read extensive literature on the topic. After trying several methods in vain, I found the right track thanks to the concept of protein diets, which I have gradually &lt;strong&gt;adapted to east and central European eating habits&lt;/strong&gt; while optimizing to make it easier to follow.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			I requested help from doctors and nutritionists with whom we tested the practical impact of our experimental theories and negative experience with other dieting methods.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			We created a program based on our observations and named it the &lt;strong&gt;DANNY CHANDLER’S AMAZING SWISS SLIMMING CONCEPT&lt;/strong&gt;, which covers everything that we expected of it.  It’s systematically &lt;strong&gt;effective, absolutely safe&lt;/strong&gt; when indicated correctly, and extremely practical (it’s based on instant meals, so there is no need for sophisticated cooking) and &lt;strong&gt;absolutely harmless for your health&lt;/strong&gt;, meaning no chemicals (its main ingredients are proteins based on milk, soy, peas etc.).
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			&lt;b&gt;The result is a program that not only gives the client means to fight their extra weight, but gives them a way to win it once and for all.&lt;/b&gt;
		</t2>
	</slimming>

	<partnership>
		<h1>Partnership</h1>
		<t1>
			My collaborators and I have decided to make &lt;strong&gt;DANNY CHANDLER’S AMAZING SWISS SLIMMING CONCEPT&lt;/strong&gt; available to all &lt;strong&gt;serious interested parties&lt;/strong&gt;, who’d like to promote a time-proven weight-loss method that we adapted to a different „target audience“, with entirely different eating habits and consumer reflexes than those from the USA (where the protein diet was created), and France (the European country in which the protein diet developer the most). Our partner will gain precious &lt;strong&gt;know-how&lt;/strong&gt;, which will help them avoid a number of mistakes that we made while trying to find the perfect formula.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			It’s not a franchise, despite how it may look like at first sight. Our goal isn’t to make tens or hundreds of small centers that we can’t even care for properly at the end of the day. Our goal is to propose our project to an &lt;strong&gt;ambitious partner who’d like full exclusivity in his country&lt;/strong&gt;, one that would be able to develop it in grand style. Our partners &lt;strong&gt;do not pay us any registration fee&lt;/strong&gt;, we do not force them to make contractually determined sales, &lt;strong&gt;we do not set business goals to them&lt;/strong&gt;.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			Why? Because the effectiveness of our weight-loss program is so shocking that we don’t need those.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			We offer our partners &lt;strong&gt;consultations, conferences and organizational support&lt;/strong&gt; and when their business develops we start participating reasonably while searching for other ways to expand this uncommon weight-loss method.
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			Should you consider working with us, do not hesitate to contact us and we’ll gladly discuss the details of a possible collaboration.
		</t1>

		<h2>Why with us </h2>
		<t2>
			People and parties interested in doing business in the area of weight-loss have to face a lot of unknown…
 			&lt;ul class="small-text-indentation no-list-style"&gt;
			&lt;li class="text-justify margin-top-20"&gt;&lt;strong class="margin-left-20 font-size-20"&gt;Choosing the right method&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;

			&lt;p class="text-justify ¸small-text-indentation margin-top-20"&gt;First and foremost, one has to choose a suitable and effective method from the incredible amount of methods that are out there.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;ul class="small-text-indentation no-list-style"&gt;
			&lt;li class="text-justify margin-top-20"&gt;&lt;strong class="margin-left-20 font-size-20"&gt;Choosing the right products&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;

			&lt;p class="text-justify small-text-indentation margin-top-20"&gt;
			If one decides that the protein diet is the most considerate, reliable and healthy way to lose weight, then he must start with a set of protein products, usually united under a brand name thus becoming a brand dealer… or he finds a manufacturer and creates his own brand… But which manufacturer? But how to decide which one? And how does one know if it’s a legitimate one and their products are going to work? And if it theoretically works, how does one continue to promote the products when any activity from the manufacturer is over once he produces and sells you their products….  How to present the products? To whom, what target audience? And what to do should any problems arise? Patients are losing weight… report medical problems during the diet… where is the mistake? I have products in my warehouse that nobody wants, what do I do with them?
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			Choosing the right product is simply not enough to reach your goal.
			&lt;/p&gt;
		</t2>

		<h3>Choosing the right program</h3>
		<t3>
			It’s possible to attend a franchise faire trade show and buy a certified method. But what if it turns out to be full of empty promises? Maybe it doesn’t work as well as it was said to…
			&lt;br &gt;
			The franchised project has already been paid for, work premises have been rented and personnel has been hired and you start to feel the weight of the investment…
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			So what do we, at &lt;strong&gt;DANNY CHANDLER’S AMAZING SWISS SLIMMING CONCEPT&lt;/strong&gt; offer? How do we differ from our competitors?
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;ul class="text-indentation"&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;No fees in advance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;A personalized approach &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;Long-term professional assistance with special emphasis on how to apply the program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;Assistance should one decide to find his own manufacturer should our partner choose to create his own brand &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;Consulting when it comes to choosing your portfolio, choosing the right media to advertise, marketing etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;Lectures and medical supervision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;A know-how of 20 years and a serious background provided by its Swiss maternal company… &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="text-justify"&gt;&lt;span class="margin-left-20 font-size-16"&gt;Many other things distinguish us from similar vendors of „guaranteed“ methods and „miraculous“ weight-loss cases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
			&lt;br &gt;
			&lt;br &gt;

			Would you like to verify yourself? &lt;a href="/contact"&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;!
		</t3>
	</partnership>

	<contact>
		<questions>Got questions?</questions>
		<t1>
			&lt;p&gt;You can contact us at : &lt;a href="mailto:info@myswissdiet.com"&gt;info@myswissdiet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Do not hesitate to contact us should you:&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;ul&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Like to lose weight in a healthy manner. We will direct you towards a verified dieting center.&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Want to work with us and develop the concept in your region or country.&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Have more questions regarding the functioning of the program.&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</t1>
		<contactus>Contact us</contactus>
		<name>Your name:</name>
		<email>Your e-mail:</email>
		<message>Your message:</message>
		<send>Send</send>
		<success>Message successfully sent</success>
	</contact>
	<footer>
		<copy>All rights reserved.</copy>
	</footer>

</langText>
